* [Scams](https://bodascambaits.net/scams/) Menu Toggle

Main Menu

* [Scams](https://bodascambaits.net/scams/) Menu Toggle

Privacy Policy
==============

Who we are
----------

Our website address is: https://bodascambaits.net.

Comments
--------

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Media
-----

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

Cookies
-------

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Embedded content from other websites
------------------------------------

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

Who we share your data with
---------------------------

If you request a password reset, your IP address will be included in the reset email.

How long we retain your data
----------------------------

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

Spread the love

Login in
--------

Posts
-----

* [Inside the World of PCH Lottery Scams: How Jamaican Scammers Operate](https://bodascambaits.net/2024/03/15/inside-the-world-of-pch-lottery-scams-how-jamaican-scammers-operate/)

Comments
--------

* [A Comparison of Jamaican vs. Indian Scammers - Boda Scambaits](https://bodascambaits.net/2024/03/22/a-comparison-of-jamaican-vs-indian-scammers/) on [Inside the World of PCH Lottery Scams: How Jamaican Scammers Operate](https://bodascambaits.net/2024/03/15/inside-the-world-of-pch-lottery-scams-how-jamaican-scammers-operate/#comment-65)
* Sashank on [NanoBaiter](https://bodascambaits.net/2022/04/26/nanobaiter/#comment-57)
* [Boda Scambaits](https://bodascambaits.net/) on [Unmasking the Ultimate Troll: A Scambaiting Extraordinaire](https://bodascambaits.net/2023/09/01/unmasking-the-ultimate-troll-a-scambaiting-extraordinaire/#comment-54)
* BentoBrocke on [Unmasking the Ultimate Troll: A Scambaiting Extraordinaire](https://bodascambaits.net/2023/09/01/unmasking-the-ultimate-troll-a-scambaiting-extraordinaire/#comment-53)
* [Help Needed, Apply Within. - Boda Scambaits](https://bodascambaits.net/2023/06/23/help-needed-apply-within/) on [Protect Yourself From Being Scammed](https://bodascambaits.net/2023/01/25/protect-yourself-from-being-scammed/#comment-52)

Copyright © 2024 Boda Scambaits

The Cookie Monster Says....... We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.  

To hell with convenience!.

Cookie SettingsACCEPT

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

SAVE & ACCEPT

Scroll to Top
